

Andrea Feliziani

www.andreafeliziani.com

□ andrea.feliziani97@gmail.com

\$ 3396443800

Milan, Italiy

Skills

UX/UI HTML

Figma CSS

Adobe Photoshop Javascript

Adobe Illustrator Bootstrap

Adobe indesign Wordpress

Adobe XD Typescript

React

Languages

Suite Microsoft

Italian Fluen

English B1

Refrences



github.com/Felix2897



Linkedin.com/in/andrea-feliziani

Presentation

I am a **UI/UX Designer** and **Front-end Developer** with a solid technical foundation gained at the Technical Institute in Computer Science. I further refined my skills through a three-year degree in Product Design from Ascoli Piceno, integrating my technical background with a broader perspective on design.

My academic journey continued with a Master's degree in Communication Theory and Technology at the University of Milano-Bicocca, where I deepened my knowledge of communication principles and developed practical skills in Front-end and UI/UX Design.

Education

IT Specialist

2011 - 2016

• <u>High school</u>, Itis Eustachio Divini - San Severino Marche

Industrial and Environmental Design

2018 - 2022

• <u>Bachelor's Degree</u>, University of Camerino

Teoria e tecnologia della comunicazione 2022 - 2024

• Master's Degree, University of Milano-Bicocca

Work Experience

UI|UX Designer - Front End Developer

2024

University of Milano-Bicocca

• Internship during the second year of the master's degree from January 24 to June 24, 2024

UI|UX Designer - Front End Developer

2024

IBS,Tolentino

Contract work, full-remote position from December 2023 to July 2024

Programmatore Software ERP

2015

IBS, Tolentino, Marche

Internship during the fourth year of high school

Election Official Secretary

2016-oggi

Municipality of San Severino Marche



Andrea Feliziani

www.andreafeliziani.com

□ andrea.feliziani97@gmail.com

\$ 3396443800

Milan, Italy

Skills

UX/UI HTML
Figma CSS
Adobe Photoshop Javascript
Adobe Illustrator Bootstrap
Adobe indesign Wordpress
Adobe XD Typescript
Suite Microsoft React

Languages

Italian Fluent

English B1

Certifications

• Web Developer Learn	2024
• Figma Learn	2024
• Gamification for UX Designer Fastweb Digital Academy	2024
• UX/UI Design: attività e competenze Fastweb Digital Academy	2024
• Adobe Illustrator Udemy	2022
• Adobe Photoshop Udemy	2022
• Microsoft Excel Udemy	2023
• Corso Coding Alteredu.it	2022
• Corso Lim Alteredu.it	2022
• Corso Tablet Alteredu.it	2022
• 24 Cfu formativi Unicam	2022

Refrences



github.com/Felix2897



Linkedin.com/in/andrea-feliziani